Princeton Football Films Collection, 1935-2012(bulk 1935-1990): Finding Aid AC297
University Archives
- Princeton Football Film Reels, 1935-1990; 2187 items
  - 1968-1969, 73 items
    - 1969 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1969 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1969 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1969 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1969 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1969 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1969 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1969 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1969 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1969 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1969 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1969 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1969 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1969 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1969 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1969 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1969 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1969 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1969 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1969 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1969 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1969 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1969 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1969 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1969 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1969 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1969 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1969 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1969 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1969 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1969 Yale (Offense 3), 1 item (Item 1969 Yale (Offense 3))
  - 1970-1975, 243 items
    - 1970 Boston College (Defense), 1 item (Item 1970 Boston College (Defense))
    - 1970 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1970 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1970 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1970 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1970 Brown (Offense 4), 1 item (Item 1970 Brown (Offense 4))
    - 1970 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1970 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1970 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1970 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1970 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1970 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1970 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1970 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1970 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1970 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1970 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1970 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1970 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1970 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1970 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1970 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1970 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1970 Dartmouth (Offense2), 1 item (Item 1970 Dartmouth (Offense2))
    - 1970 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1970 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1970 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1970 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1970 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1970 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1970 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1970 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1970 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1970 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1970 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1970 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1970 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1970 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1970 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1970 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1970 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1971 Brown (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1971 Brown (Full Game 1))
    - 1971 Brown (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1971 Brown (Full Game 2))
    - 1971 Brown (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1971 Brown (Full Game 3))
    - 1971 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1971 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1971 Colgate (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1971 Colgate (Full Game 1))
    - 1971 Colgate (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1971 Colgate (Full Game 2))
    - 1971 Colgate (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1971 Colgate (Full Game 3))
    - 1971 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1971 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1971 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1971 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1971 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1971 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1971 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1971 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1971 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1971 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1971 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1971 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1971 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1971 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1971 Cornell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1971 Cornell (Full Game 4))
    - 1971 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1971 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1971 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1971 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1971 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1971 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1971 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1971 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1971 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1971 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1971 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1971 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1971 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1971 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1971 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1971 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1971 Harvard (Full Game 5), 1 item (Item 1971 Harvard (Full Game 5))
    - 1971 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1971 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1971 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1971 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1971 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1971 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1971 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1971 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1971 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1971 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1971 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1971 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1971 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1971 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1971 Yale (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1971 Yale (Full Game 4))
    - 1972 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1972 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1972 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1972 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1972 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1972 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1972 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1972 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1972 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1972 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1972 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1972 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1972 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1972 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1972 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1972 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1972 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1972 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1972 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1972 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1972 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1972 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1972 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1972 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1972 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1972 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1972 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1972 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1972 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1972 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1972 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1972 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1972 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1972 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1972 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1972 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1972 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1972 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1972 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1972 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1972 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1972 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1972 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1973 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1973 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1973 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1973 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1973 Colgate (Defense1), 1 item (Item 1973 Colgate (Defense1))
    - 1973 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1973 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1973 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1973 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1973 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1973 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1973 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1973 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1973 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1973 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1973 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1973 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1973 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1973 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1973 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1973 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1973 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1973 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1973 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1973 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1973 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1973 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1973 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1973 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1973 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1973 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1973 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1973 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1973 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1973 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1973 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1973 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1973 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1973 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1973 Rutgers (Defense 3), 1 item (Item 1973 Rutgers (Defense 3))
    - 1973 Rutgers (Defense 3), 1 item (Item 1973 Rutgers (Defense 3))
    - 1973 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1973 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1973 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1973 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1973 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1973 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1973 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1973 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1974 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1974 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1974 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1974 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1974 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1974 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1974 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1974 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1974 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1974 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1974 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1974 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1974 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1974 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1974 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1974 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1974 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1974 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1974 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1974 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1974 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1974 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1974 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1974 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1974 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1974 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1974 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1974 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1974 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1974 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1974 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1974 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1974 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1975 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1975 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1975 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1975 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1975 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1975 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1975 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1975 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1975 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1975 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1975 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1975 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1975 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1975 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1975 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1975 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1975 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1975 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1975 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1975 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1975 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1975 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1975 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1975 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1975 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1975 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1975 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1975 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1975 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1975 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1975 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1975 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1975 Cornell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1975 Cornell (Full Game 4))
    - 1975 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1975 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1975 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1975 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1975 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1975 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1975 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1975 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1975 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1975 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1975 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1975 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1975 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1975 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1975 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1975 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1975 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1975 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1975 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1975 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1975 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1975 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1975 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1975 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1975 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1975 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1975 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1975 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1975 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1975 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1975 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1975 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1975 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1975 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1975 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1975 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1975 Yale (Offense 1))
  - 1976-1977, 198 items
    - 1976 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Brown (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Brown (Full Game 1))
    - 1976 Brown (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Brown (Full Game 2))
    - 1976 Brown (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1976 Brown (Full Game 3))
    - 1976 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1976 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1976 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Colgate (Miscellaneous), 1 item (Item 1976 Colgate (Miscellaneous))
    - 1976 Colgate (Offense), 1 item (Item 1976 Colgate (Offense))
    - 1976 Colgate (Offense), 1 item (Item 1976 Colgate (Offense))
    - 1976 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1976 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1976 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1976 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1976 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1976 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1976 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1976 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1976 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1976 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1976 Cornell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1976 Cornell (Full Game 4))
    - 1976 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1976 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1976 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1976 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1976 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1976 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1976 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1976 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1976 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1976 Dartmouth (Offense), 1 item (Item 1976 Dartmouth (Offense))
    - 1976 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1976 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1976 Harvard (Defense 2))